estherperel.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  
Effective Date: April 18, 2016  

The following Privacy Policy governs the online information collection practices of Esther Perel Global Media LLC (“we,”“us”or the “Company”). Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you while you are using the [www.rekindlingdesire.com](http://www.rekindlingdesire.com/) and [www.programs.estherperel.com](http://www.programs.estherperel.com/) websites (each, the “Site”), and the ways in which we use this information. This Privacy Policy, including our children’s privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means (for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail).

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of our Site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy. Because the internet is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we will post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this Site and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the Site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified.

This Site strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use personally identifying information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number, credit card information) subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

How We Collect and Use Information   
We may collect and store personal or other information that you voluntarily supply to us online while using the Site (e.g., while on the Site or in responding via email to a feature provided on the Site). This Site only contacts individuals who specifically request that we do so or in the event that they have signed up to receive our free newsletters or have purchased one of our products. This Site collects personally identifying information from our users during online registration and online purchasing. Generally, this information includes name and e-mail address for registration to receive our free newsletters and name, postal address, and credit card information when purchasing our products. All of this information is provided to us by you.

We also collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate online through the Site. For example, we may collect information about your computer’s or mobile’s connection to the internet, which allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you, to measure traffic on the Site, and to personalize your experience on the Site. We also may use a standard feature found in browser software called a “cookie” to enhance your experience with the Site. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us deliver advertisements, identify how many unique users visit us, and track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the Site where you may have entered preference information before. The Site also may use web beacons (single-pixel graphic files also known as “transparent GIFs”) to access cookies and to count users who visit the Site or open HTML-formatted email messages.

We use the information we collect from you while you are using the Site in a variety of ways, including using the information to customize features. We also may provide your information to third parties, such as service providers and contractors, for a variety of purposes. Unless you inform us in accordance with the process described below, we reserve the right to use, and to disclose to third parties, all of the information collected from and about you while you are using the Site in any way and for any purpose, such as to enable us or a third party to provide you with information about products and services. If you do not wish your information to be used for these purposes,you must send a letter to the online privacy coordinator whose address is listed at the end of this Privacy Policy requesting to be taken off any lists of information that may be used for these purposes or that may be given or sold to third-parties.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties online —for example on message boards, comments, chat areas, blogs,or through email—that information can be seen, collected and used by others besides us. We cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information.

The Site also includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third-party products or services through the Site, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

We may also make some content, products and services available through our Site through cooperative relationships with third-party providers, where the brands of our provider partner appear on the Site in connection with such content, products and/or services. We may share with our provider partner any information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in cooperation with our provider partner. In some cases, the provider partner may collect information from you directly, in which cases the privacy policy of our provider partner may apply to the provider partner’s use of your information. The privacy policy of our provider partners may differ from ours. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners, you should contact the provider partner directly for more information.

Be aware that we may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of the Site or the public.

Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event that we sell some or all of our assets, or one or more of our websites is acquired by another company, information about our users may be among the transferred assets.

How Do We Store Your Information?  
Your personal information is stored in electronic databases. Your personal information can only be accessed by those who work for the Company and who help manage the Site.

All of the newsletters or emails that are sent to you by this Site include an unsubscribe link in them. You can remove yourself at any time from our newsletters or mailing list by clicking on the unsubscribe link that can be found in every communication that we send you.

User Generated Feedback  
We value hearing from our users, and are always interested in learning about ways we can make our Site and services even better. Any feedback, comments, reviews, ideas or suggestions to us regarding the Site, the Workshops and our services is entirely voluntary. Any such feedback that you provide to will be the sole and exclusive property of the Company and you hereby irrevocably assign to us all of your right, title and interest in and to all such feedback. We will be free to use such feedback as we see fit and without any obligation to you.

Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance(COPPA)  
No one under the age of 18 is authorized to use the services offered by our Site, and we do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA. 

If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of 18 as part of the Site, we will delete such information from our records. 

Notice to Non-U.S. Residents   
It is important to note that the Site and its servers are operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using the Site and by providing us information when using our services, you hereby irrevocably consent to this transfer and our use of the information and data provided by you in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

California Residents -Do Not Track Notice  
We do not monitor, recognize, or honor any behavioral advertising opt-out or do not track mechanisms, including general web browser “Do Not Track” settings and signals.

Disclaimer  
This Privacy Policy may be changed at any time at our discretion. If we should update this policy, we will post the updates to this page on the Site.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please direct them to support@rekindlingdesire.com
